

CURRICULUM VITAE RAHMATUL RAMADHANI

+6289-9092-9826 || rahmatulramadhani06@gmail.com || linkedin.com/in/rahmatulramadhani || github.com/Rahmatuldani

Jl. Dr. Saharjo GG Bakti VII, Manggarai, South Jakarta

WEB DEVELOPMENT | SOFTWARE ENGINEER

I am a programmer who understands the fundamentals in web development, likes to work in a team, fast learner, has high curiosity and passion in website development. I have a work interest in making web-based applications, machine learning, and data analysis. Has 2 years of experience creating Full-stack applications using the Laravel framework, and creating applications using Node JS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmer Internship, Agung Hospital Jakarta

March 2021 - April 2021

Assist the hospital in making web-based information system technology. Job Description :

• Create a web-based Hospital Information System application using Laravel

Programmer Internship, Department of Manpower and Transmigration West Sumatra

April 2021 – May 2021

Assist the Department of Manpower and Transmigration in making web-based information system technology.

Job Description:

- Create a web-based Job Market Information Reporting application using Laravel
- Assist employees in making employee salary documents

ORGANIZATION

Web Development, UPN Information Technology Club

February 2019 - February 2021

Assist members of the organization in providing learning material and making application of website development. Job Description :

- Create an interactive and integrated web application
- Learn SDLC (System Development Live Cycle) based on SWEBOK (Software Engineering Body of Knowledge)

EDUCATION

Informatics

Hard Skill

Universitas Pembangunan Nasional "Veteran" Yogyakarta

2018 - 2022

GPA 3.39

Sains

Senior High School 13th Padang

2015 - 2018

SKILLS

• Web Development (HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP)

- Web Framework (Laravel, Codelgniter, Node JS)
- Database Management (MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB)
- Programming Language (C/C++, Java, Python, Golang)
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point, Access)

Soft Skill

Language

- Problem Solving
- Fast Learner
- Curiosity
- Indonesian
- English

REFERENCE

Siti Rafika Arman

Product Analyst - Zi.Care Jakarta

 $+6285-3766-99542 \ / \ +6289-5702-927787 \ / \ arman.sitirafika@gmail.com \ / \ www.linkedin.com/in/sitirafikaarman \ Jl. \ Dr. \ Saharjo \ GG \ Bakti \ VII, \ Manggarai, \ South \ Jakarta$